Track 4.3 Unit 4
Bài 4.3 Đơn vị 4
Language in use Activity 1
Ngôn ngữ sử dụng Bài tập 1
Listen and tick the box
Nghe và đánh dấu vào ô
Let's make a pasta salad.
Hãy làm sa lát mì ống nhé.
Good idea!
Ý hay!
How much chicken is there?
Có bao nhiêu gà?
There's a lot!
Có rất nhiều!
Here, some for you and some for me.
Đây, một ít cho bạn và một ít cho mình.
OK
Được
How many tomatoes are there?
Có bao nhiêu cà chua?
There aren't many, but that's OK.
Không có nhiều, nhưng cũng được.
OK
Được
How much cheese is there?
Có bao nhiêu phô mai?
There isn't much, but I don't like a lot of cheese.
Không có nhiều, nhưng mình không thích nhiều phô mai.
OK
Được
Hmm, delicious!
Hmm, ngon quá!
OK
Được
How many mushrooms are there?
Có bao nhiêu nấm?
There are lots of mushrooms!
Có rất nhiều nấm!
Great! I like mushrooms!
Tuyệt! Mình thích nấm!